londonticketbox.co.uk 2017-09-16

# London Ticket Box - Event tickets and online box office - Privacy Policy

#### **This Privacy Policy applies to the sites and apps where it appears.**

This Policy describes how we treat personal information we collect both online and offline. This includes on our websites or in our apps. It also includes at our box offices or in phone or email interactions you have with us.

**Your IP Address**

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer the Site. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information about you. Your IP address may also be used to assist in the detection of fraud and we shall have the right to pass this information to the polices.

#### **Cookies**

A cookie is a small text file that is saved on the hard drive of the computer used when you enter some areas of our Site. Cookies are used to keep track of what is in the shopping cart as well as for compiling statistics on the usage of the ticket shop in order to continually improve the offer for the user. London Ticket Box does not use technologies that link accumulating information with user data through cookies to determine the identity of the user. The Site can be used without cookies, however, if you choose to disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent, you may not be able to access some areas of the Site.

#### **Information We Request Directly From You**

Our Site's registration forms, order forms and other forms may require you to give us personal information (like your name, address and/or email address). You must register on our site to order tickets, and you will be asked to provide financial information so your order may be processed. You may retrieve and modify data saved to enable your use of the Site via your user account at any time. Under certain circumstances, personal data can only be deleted following a certain period of time due to legal or contractual storage obligations. In this case, the affected data will be locked until the time of deletion. You information is only collected when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to a newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form or enter information on our site.

#### **How We Use Personal Information**

Your personal information is shared between London Ticket Box and the Promoter or Venue for the particular event for which you are buying tickets in accordance with this Privacy Policy and London Ticket Box's contractual relationship with the Promoter or Venue. Your personal information is used by us to contact you by post, phone or by email when necessary in connection with transactions entered by you on the Site. We will not use your personal information for communications not associated with your transactions without your explicit consent. We will not pass your data to third parties unless you provide your explicit consent.

#### **Opting Out**

You may opt out of any of London Ticket Box's regular email contact at any time even if you have previously indicated your consent to such contact at some other time.

#### **How We Use Financial Information**

Financial information that is collected is used to authorise payment and bill you for products and services. When you make a purchase on the Site, your consent is given to provide your financial or personal information to those third parties necessary to process your transactions with us, such as credit card companies, banks and the companies that handle shipping on our behalf. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Except as provided above, we will not share financial information with third parties without your prior consent.

#### **Disclosure of Your Personal Information and Financial Information in Compliance with Laws**

We may release your personal information or financial information when we believe it is necessary to comply with laws or regulations, to assist law enforcement, to enforce the terms under which you transacted with London Ticket Box, or to protect the rights, property or safety of London Ticket Box, users of the Site or others.

#### **Other web sites**

This Site may contain links to other web sites, details of which are provided for information only. London Ticket Box has no responsibility for such sites and nor does it have responsibility for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites or for the privacy policies and practices of other third parties, and you should be careful to read those web sites' privacy policies independently.

#### **Our Security Precautions**

This Site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We use 128 bit industry standard Secure Server Software (SSL) for your transactions with us. It encrypts all of your personal information, including credit card number, name, and address, so that it cannot be read as the information travels over the Internet.

If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy statement, you can contact us at [info@Londonticketbox.co.uk](mailto:info@Londonticketbox.co.uk).

#### **Consumer Protection**

These General Terms and Conditions (Internet) are subject to the relevant provisions of The Consumer Protection (Distance Selling) Regulations 2000.

#### **Social Network plug-ins**

Our web site hosts social plug-ins for the many social networks.

When a web page containing a social plug-in (such as the ‘Like/Recommend’ or 'Tweet' button) is accessed, the user’s browser connects to the social networks servers and the content required for the social plug-ins is downloaded. The operator of the social network receives the web address of the web site accessed by the user, the date and time of access and the IP address of the user amongst other information. If the user is logged into their social network account, the social network may be able to relate the visit to that page to the user’s social network account. If the user clicks the social network button inside our web site, this information may also be transferred to the social network and stored there. If the user does not wish this information to be sent to the social network, he or she must log out of their social network before visiting our web site. If the user of the web site is not a member of the social network, there is still a possibility that the social network will identify and store the user’s IP address.

London Ticket Box has no control over the content of the plug-ins or of the information transferred to social networks. The purpose and scope of data collection, the further processing and use of the data by the social networks and the user’s rights and setting options to protect the user’s privacy can be found in the privacy policies of the networks, for example: 

Facebook privacy policy at http://www.facebook.com/policy.php  
Twitter privacy policy at http://twitter.com/privacy

Last update: 01.05.2015

####
